https://www.amgad.com/page/privacy-policy.html

HomePrivacy policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Our Customers
AMGAD Inc. is committed to providing the most value for our customers along with the best customer service both online and offline. To achieve our goal, we ask you to provide certain information that allows us to process your order and assist you in obtaining exactly what you want. Your security, protection and privacy is important to us here at AMGAD. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice clearly explaining our online information practices.
Registration and Collection Of Information
AMGAD and related companies (collectively "AMGAD"), operate amgad.com. When you register or request a price quote from our website you are prompted to provide us with certain personal information about yourself and/or your firm or company. The terms and User Agreement set forth herein (the "Terms") constitute a legally binding agreement between AMGAD and you ("You" or "Your") regarding the terms on which AMGAD offers You access to its Website and Service. Your use of the Website or Service constitutes acceptance of these Terms. Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.
Notice About Cookies
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When You visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if Your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect Your privacy) Your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to You, not the cookies sent to you by other site. As You browse our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate You from other viewers so Your account is only available to You. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to continuously improve our Web site and better serve our customers.
Use Of Your Information?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of providing customer service administering and expanding our business activities. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify You about important changes to our Web site, new services, educational information and special offers we think You will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if You do not wish to receive these offers by logging into your account and changing your settings at My AMGAD, or by calling our office at 212-719-4111.
Sharing Information With Third Parties
As a private company, AMGAD goes to great lengths to safeguard our customer’s information. Our web site may use a third party service provider to serve e-mails on our behalf. This company uses technologies similar to those outlined above to measure the effectiveness of our e-mails and use information about Your visits to this and other Web sites so that we can provide newsletters about goods and promotions of interest to You. In no event will AMGAD sell lists of customer information to any other party for marketing purposes.
How to Update Your Personal Information
If you wish to update or remove your personal information at any time You may do so by logging into Your account My AMGAD If You do not wish to provide this information by email, or are unable to access your account, You may contact AMGAD at 212.719.4111 and our customer service representatives will be happy to make the change for You.
Copyright Protection
No logo, graphic, sound or image from any AMGAD Web site may be copied or retransmitted unless expressly permitted by AMGAD. Re-posting of information, photographs, certificates and articles from our web site is strictly forbidden and will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law. Unless otherwise noted, all web site content is © 2012 AMGAD. All rights are reserved.
INDEMNITY.
IN NO EVENT SHALL AMGAD AND/OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, SHAREHOLDERS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, PARTNERS, EMPLOYEES AND REPRESENTATIVES BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF OUR WEB SITE, DOCUMENTS, PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR INFORMATION AVAILABLE FROM THE SERVICES. THE PRODUCT LISTINGS, DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS PUBLISHED ON OUR WEB SITE COULD INCLUDE TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS.
TERMINATION OF ACCESS
AMGAD may terminate Your access to its web site content and services at if You are in breach of these terms and conditions of use, or at its sole discretion.
Google Analytics
We use a tool called "Google Analytics" to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the
Google Analytics Terms of Use and the
Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by
disabling cookies on your browser.
Saved Items (0)
Use this space to save the products you like. To add a product here, simply click the
icon.
